This video will explain to you how to quickly put on clothes for models of different body types.
First, click on the file to save as clothes.
Save the clothes files that do not contain models.
Next, open a dog model with a larger body type.
Then click on the file.
Increase clothes.
Click on Open to import this clothes file.
Add a type to choose to increase.
Click on Confirm.
After the clothes are imported, you can see that the size of the clothes needs to be adjusted.
For the size adjustment, we can use the new function of 2026.0.
The 3D model 1 key equalizer function.
First, use the adjustment panel tool.
Then select all clothing panels in the 2D window.
Increase the proportion of panels.
You can see that in the 3D window, the clothes are maintained in their original state.
The proportion has been increased.
Use the positioning tool to move the clothes to the corresponding position.
Next, you can enlarge the 2D panel again.
And when you enlarge the panel, right-click.
You can enter the proportion you want to enlarge.
Of course, you can also shrink the panels in the same proportion.
In the 3D window, you can also maintain the original state.
Then let's select the sleeve part of the panel separately.
Drag the positioning ball to put the sleeve on the dog's leg.
Check it.
Click .
Use the positioning tool to organize the shape of both clothes.
When you're done organizing the dress, the dress is finished.
The following is the display effect of this costume for models of different bodies in the same way.